ANNA JENNINGS

CONTACT

Location Los Angeles, CA (Remote)
Email annajennings.ux@gmail.com
Website www.anna-jennings.com
LinkedIn www.linkedin.com/in/anna-jennings-ux/
Phone 520-232-4990

Focused and dynamic UX/UI designer with experience as a theatre artist and producer developing plays with a focus on audience reception. Expert in identifying challenging moments, asking generative questions, iterating possible solutions, and guiding fellow artists to effective storytelling for over 50 professional productions. Responsible and dependable with consistent organization, productivity, communication, and time management skills while collaborating remotely across various platforms.

EDUCATION

UX DESIGN PROGRAM CERTIFICATE

Specialities: Frontend Development & UI

CareerFoundry - Online
In progress, expected completion August 2022

M.F.A. THEATRE ARTS

University of Arizona - Tucson, AZ

B.A. THEATRE ARTS & ENGLISH

University of Arizona - Tucson, AZ

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ARTISTIC COORDINATOR (Jan 2020 - Present) **SOUTH COAST REPERTORY,** Costa Mesa, CA

Adapted producing model from live to virtual theatre by collaborating & liaising with a cross-functional team while adhering to union rules for 10+ events, resulting in audiences of over 40% first-time ticket buyers in 2021. Represented SCR on the Orange County Theatre Guild board as a council member establishing new partnerships with 20 local theaters.

ARTISTIC MANAGER (Oct 2017 - Nov 2019) ARIZONA THEATRE COMPANY, Tucson, AZ

Implemented new post-show discussion series by moderating sessions with artists & public audiences, increasing actor participation by 50% & ticket sales by 15%.

AQUATICS MANAGER (May 2013 - Aug 2016) CITY OF KINGMAN, PARKS & RECREATION, Kingman AZ Oversaw a staff of 35 lifeguards & staff at 2 public pools by implementing new training and interfacing with public on water safety, reducing overall rescues by 20%.

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

ORANGE COUNTY REGISTRAR OF VOTERS, Santa Ana, CA Ensured secure voting process for O.C. voters by adhering to strict election laws, protocols, and regulations resulting in counting & transporting ballots securely for 3 elections: November 2020, March 2021, & June 2022.

SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

- Creativity, innovation
- Curiosity, initiative
- Written & verbal communication
- Collaboration
- Empathy, emotional intelligence
- Creative/interpretive analysis
- Critical/strategic analysis
- Flexibility, adaptability
- Responsibility, dependability

HARD SKILLS

- User research
- Information architecture
- User flows, site mapping
- Wireframing, prototyping
- Writing, UX writing
- Image editing
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

TOOLS

- AdobeXD
- InDesign
- Photoshop
- Figma
- Microsoft 365
- Google Workspace
- Zoom, Slack

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Advanced
- French Intermediate
- German Beginner